Speaker 1: The facts of this case do not lead up to there was one bomber that came into Oklahoma City and blew the building up. They didn't think it was important to talk to Strassmeyer. Who was
Speaker 2: Strassmeyer? He
Speaker 1: was taking these trips to Oklahoma, planning a
Speaker 3: bombing. And the
Speaker 4: FBI never interviewed him. Now, he was a German national.
He was a
Speaker 3: German national.
Speaker 4: Logically, the only reason I can think of that they wouldn't interview him would be that he was working for them.
Speaker 5: That would seem logical to me. I mean, McVeigh calls him two minutes after calling the Ryder Truck Company.
Speaker 1: There has to be some kind of connection, but he just disappeared. Is he
Speaker 6: still alive? Yes. Has he ever been interviewed by the FBI that you know of in person? Not to
my
Speaker 1: knowledge.